

## Georgiana-Daniela Cioiu

My name is Georgiana-Daniela Cioiu.

I am currently a student at the University of Bolton, department - Criminological and Forensic Psychology, Year 1.

I am a talkative and kindly person. My goal is to gain experience and learn new things in any field as part of a multidisciplinary team.

Date of birth: 22/04/2001 | Gender: Female | Nationality: Romanian

**Mobile:** (+44) 7575789905

Email address: cioiu\_georgiana@yahoo.com

O Home: 23 Cardigan Street, Asthon-On-Ribble, PR2 2AS Preston, United Kingdom

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Waiter/waitress

08/08/2016 - 04/11/2020

Oconstanta, Romania

At the same time as high school, I worked part-time as a waitress. I obtained many qualities through this job and helped me to develop my personality.

#### Shop assistant

10/04/2016 - 01/08/2016

Oconstanta, Romania

## **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

#### "Virgil Madgearu" High School

Services department, specialization of Procurement and Contracting Tehnician  $15/09/2016-20/05/2020\,$ 

Aleea Melodiei 3, Constanța, Constanta, Romania

#### University of Bofton

Criminological and Forensic Psychology

15/01/2021 - Current

#### Urania association

Astronomical course

01/06/2016 - 02/09/2016

#### Civil Association for first aid and disaster response(A.C.P.I.D)

First aid class

12/12/2015 - 10/02/2016

Fantastic English

# **LANGUAGE SKILLS** Mother tongue(s) Romanian Other language(s) **English** Listening B2 Reading B2 Spoken interaction $\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\circ$ $\circ$ Spoken production B2 Writing B2

## **DIGITAL SKILLS**

#### Other

Video conferencing experience (Zoom, Skype)

Microsoft word, microsoft excel, power point

Social Media (Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, LinkedIn)

Good listener and communicator

Creativity

Motivated

Decision-making

Gmail

### **DRIVING LICENCE**



В

Report inappropriate content